<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Philadelphia Real Estate Video Blog with Jeremy Bowers</title>
    <description>Jeremy Bowers, a top Real Estate Agent in Philadelphia, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:25:12 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:25:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s going on in the Philadelphia real estate market?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/tjnV6Zx-_u8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s going on in the Philadelphia real estate market? Today, our agents will be discussing where they think the market will be heading in 2019, and what that means for buyers and sellers. We’ll be discussing not only this, but ways we can better utilize our current market to help achieve our goals and help those around us. To learn more, watch this short video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you have any other questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We’d be happy to help you.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 17:15:03 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-going-on-in-the-philadelphia-real-estate-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/whats-going-on-in-the-philadelphia-real-estate-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mike McCann Joins KW</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/6UTa0h160lw?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the last 31 years, there has been no team or group of real estate agents that have dominated a region throughout the country quite like the Mike McCann Team has.  The opportunity to collaborate and work alongside one of the most dynamic figures in real estate will be a tremendous asset for our brokerage, agents and the overall future at Keller Williams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are proud to officially announce that Mike McCann “The Real Estate Man” along with Jim Onesti, Paul Chin, Bibe Chin, Stuart C Cohen, Margo Weil Sorrenti, Lauren Acker Kratz, Ame Goldman, Lynda Krevitz, Rich Fravel, Bryanna Carzo, Ed Foy, Daniel Evenchen, Melissa Gehman, Mike Goldstein, Kate McCann, Arvind Balaji, Ryan McCann, Carson Merine, Andrea Boelter, Chloe Alvarado-McCann, Melanie Mcconnell, Cyndi McCann, Karen McCormick, Beth McLean, Julie McCann, Jessica Kalup, Asa Kurland, Joyce Caldwell, will be joining the KW Philly team! We welcome you all and are excited to take our company to even higher heights!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike earned his status as “The Real Estate Man” by utilizing his extensive knowledge and experience to consistently provide quality service for his clients, establishing a remarkably positive reputation within Philadelphia.&lt;br /&gt;Mike holds CRS, GRI, and Associate Broker designations. He has also served on the GPAR Board of Directors, and on the Grievance Committee of the same board. He started in real estate because he realized that “The harder you work, the more you can earn”. Mike has stayed in real estate because he loves people: meeting them, working with them, helping them reach their goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Few people love Philadelphia more than Mike McCann. His enthusiasm for the city and its residents is contagious! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some accolades:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2018, The Mike McCann Team settled 782 properties, over $367 million in real estate transactions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike McCann has been ranked in the top 50 agents out of 2 million agents nationwide by The Wall Street Journal for the past 12 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The #1 REALTOR® in Philadelphia for 31 years, Mike has been awarded more Top Selling Awards by the Philadelphia Board of Realtors than anyone in its 100-year history.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike has also been featured on CNBC Open House about Philadelphia Real Estate. He has been quoted in the Wall Street Journal, New York Times and Philadelphia Inquirer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Mike McCann Team has been ranked #1 or #2 nationwide by Berkshire Hathaway Home Services (BHHS) for the past 17 years.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mike was extremely straightforward and sincere with his reasoning on joining the KW Philly team.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; ”Recently I have seen the biggest changes in the real estate market in my 30 year career. I felt it was important to align myself and my team with the most forward-thinking, visionary leader and company in the business, Gary Keller and Keller Williams.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moving to Keller Williams Philly will allow my agents to have the most state-of the art technology and training, while giving our clients the best personal service and the most aggressive marketing to get their real estate needs met quickly. I am so excited and I am sure this new energy and focus will drive The Mike McCann Team for 10, 20 years and beyond!”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 16:35:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/mike-mccann-joins-kw.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/mike-mccann-joins-kw.html</guid>
        
        <category>Testimonials</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Being Part Time VS. Full Time</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/RQvFuMul4Zo?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s the difference between being a part time agent, versus being a full time agent?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the real estate business, many people choose to do it part time. The most effective way to be successful as a part time agent is to pretend as though it’s an hourly job. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I started as a part time agent, I would block off certain nights of the week, for four hour time-blocks. I would focus on lead generation, marketing, or showing houses.  It allowed me to accelerate really quickly, but many people don’t follow that path. If you don’t time block and map out your goals, you won’t see success. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking about going full time, you need to align yourself with a brokerage that will support you in your endeavor. To learn more, watch this short video.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 09:46:03 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/being-part-time-vs-full-time.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/being-part-time-vs-full-time.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should I Join a Team?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/FMqE1x9iE0s?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I often get the question, “Should I join a team or not?”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The answer depends on what you want. There are plenty of benefits to joining a team, just as there are benefits with staying independent. There’s no right or wrong answer, but to help you determine what is right for you, watch this short video.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 09:41:32 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/should-i-join-a-team.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/should-i-join-a-team.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What to Look for in a Brokerage</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/mCcq68iCGi8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What should you be looking for when you’re thinking about aligning yourself with a brokerage? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It depends entirely on your situation, and there are three questions you can ask to determine the answer. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;What do you want?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;How are you going to get there?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;What is your why?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn about choosing the right brokerage for you, watch this short video.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 09:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-to-look-for-in-a-brokerage.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-to-look-for-in-a-brokerage.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate Coaching</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Get Your Real Estate License</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/2GrEEOsRWzg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you go about getting your real estate license? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It depends on what state you’re living or working in. The first step is going to real estate schools, for which there are many available. To learn more about getting your real estate license, watch this short video.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 09:35:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-get-your-real-estate-license.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-to-get-your-real-estate-license.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate Coaching</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who Is Jeremy Bowers?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/RCCYa7eQl2s?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who is Jeremy Bowers? Today, we’ll be discussing how I got into real estate, and journey I took to become successful. I also want to discuss how I can help you succeed in your real estate career. To get to know me and KW Philly, watch this short video.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 03:50:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/who-is-jeremy-bowers.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/who-is-jeremy-bowers.html</guid>
        
        <category>About Me</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
