<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Philadelphia Real Estate Podcast with Jeremy Bowers</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Keller Williams Philly - your professional Philadelphia Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Jeremy Bowers</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2019-01-17 14:13:16 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Jeremy Bowers</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Philadelphia, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>jeremycbowers@kw.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Jeremy Bowers</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Jeremy Bowers</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Philadelphia, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Philadelphia Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Keller Williams Philly - your professional Philadelphia Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Benefits of Owning Your Business</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-benefits-of-owning-your-business.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Jeremy Bowers</author>
        <pubDate>2019-01-15 15:42:45 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

As a real estate agent, what’s the difference between renting and owning your business? Why should you strive to own your business instead of rent it?

To answer the first question, renting a business is the more traditional industry model. You typically start by owning 50% of the business and build your way up to owning 90%. However, you’re still paying rent in the form of a franchise fee. Basically, it’s like renting an apartment—you never technically own it, and you’re never at a point where you’re earning equity.

When you own a business, you get set at a certain percentage and pay a firm fee, but you make 100% of the profit. You might start off making 70%, but you’d eventually end up at 100%. By owning your business, you also no longer have to pay a franchise fee. Here at KW Philly, you’d pay a 6% firm fee, but that’s capped at $3,000.

When you rent a business, a traditional firm will take 20% of your revenue. If you generated $300,000 a year, for instance, your firm would take $60,000. On top of that, you’re looking at paying a franchise fee of $18,000, so in total, you’re paying $78,000 of that $300,000. If you owned your business, you’d only pay $28,000 of that total.

When you rent things in life, you normally get tax write-offs and other benefits from doing so. By owning your business, though, you can help make it grow and make more money by referring people to your firm. I know people who make as much as $30,000 or $40,000 a month through referral fees.

“A business owner looks at multiple revenue streams that can benefit themselves as well as their clients.”

Besides owning your business versus renting your business, there’s another option you should consider: Investing. Is anyone at your firm helping you invest in real estate? Do you have an opportunity to invest in other projects or buy a rental property? I recommend investing in at least one rental property per year. Are you around the type of people who will help you do this?

As real estate agents, we sometimes focus too much on being an agent and not enough on being a business owner. A business owner looks at multiple revenue streams that can benefit themselves as well as their clients. They also consider whether those revenue streams will impact the next generation. I refer to this as “generational disruption,” and when you own your business, you can achieve this.

When you rent your business, however, you trade time for money, and when you trade time for money, eventually everything stops.

If you’re tired of renting your business and you want to become an owner, I’d love to show you all the ways you can accomplish this. I’ve helped people generate millions of dollars in the investment game, and billions of dollars in the real estate game. Now, I’m helping people generate retirement income through their downlines.

Just give me a call or send me an email today. I look forward to hearing from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>As a real estate agent, you can help your career greatly by owning your business instead of renting it. Here’s what I mean by that.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jeremy Bowers</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>As a real estate agent, you can help your career greatly by owning your business instead of renting it. Here’s what I mean by that.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Philadelphia, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Jeremy Bowers</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Jeremy Bowers</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Keller Williams Philly - your professional Philadelphia Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
